<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<XML_DIZ_INFO>
	<MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
		<MASTER_PAD_VERSION>2.01</MASTER_PAD_VERSION>
		<MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>PADGen 2.0.1.22 http://www.padgen.org</MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>
		<MASTER_PAD_INFO>Portable Application Description, or PAD for short, is a data set that is used by shareware authors to disseminate information to anyone interested in their software products. To find out more go to http://www.asp-shareware.org/pad</MASTER_PAD_INFO>
	</MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
	<Company_Info>
		<Company_Name>DelphiDabbler</Company_Name>
		<Address_1 />
		<Address_2 />
		<City_Town>Llanarth</City_Town>
		<State_Province>Ceredigion</State_Province>
		<Zip_Postal_Code />
		<Country>UK</Country>
		<Company_WebSite_URL>http://www.delphidabbler.com/</Company_WebSite_URL>
		<Contact_Info>
			<Author_First_Name>Peter</Author_First_Name>
			<Author_Last_Name>Johnson</Author_Last_Name>
			<Author_Email>peter.johnson@openlink.org</Author_Email>
			<Contact_First_Name>Peter</Contact_First_Name>
			<Contact_Last_Name>Johnson</Contact_Last_Name>
			<Contact_Email>peter.johnson@openlink.org</Contact_Email>
		</Contact_Info>
		<Support_Info>
			<Sales_Email>peter.johnson@openlink.org</Sales_Email>
			<Support_Email>peter.johnson@openlink.org</Support_Email>
			<General_Email>peter.johnson@openlink.org</General_Email>
			<Sales_Phone />
			<Support_Phone />
			<General_Phone />
			<Fax_Phone />
		</Support_Info>
	</Company_Info>
	<Program_Info>
		<Program_Name>Resource File Unit</Program_Name>
		<Program_Version>1.0</Program_Version>
		<Program_Release_Month>09</Program_Release_Month>
		<Program_Release_Day>17</Program_Release_Day>
		<Program_Release_Year>2004</Program_Release_Year>
		<Program_Cost_Dollars>0</Program_Cost_Dollars>
		<Program_Cost_Other_Code />
		<Program_Cost_Other />
		<Program_Type>Freeware</Program_Type>
		<Program_Release_Status>New Release</Program_Release_Status>
		<Program_Install_Support>No Install Support</Program_Install_Support>
		<Program_OS_Support>Win95,Win98,WinME,WinNT 4.x,Windows2000,WinXP,Windows2003</Program_OS_Support>
		<Program_Language>English</Program_Language>
		<Program_Change_Info />
		<Program_Specific_Category>Development Tools</Program_Specific_Category>
		<Program_Category_Class>Development::Delphi</Program_Category_Class>
		<Program_Categories>Development Tools</Program_Categories>
		<Program_System_Requirements />
		<Includes_JAVA_VM>N</Includes_JAVA_VM>
		<Includes_VB_Runtime>N</Includes_VB_Runtime>
		<Includes_DirectX>N</Includes_DirectX>
		<File_Info>
			<Filename_Versioned>resfil10.zip</Filename_Versioned>
			<Filename_Previous>resfil10.zip</Filename_Previous>
			<Filename_Generic>resfile.zip</Filename_Generic>
			<Filename_Long>dd-resfile.zip</Filename_Long>
			<File_Size_Bytes>31891</File_Size_Bytes>
			<File_Size_K>31</File_Size_K>
			<File_Size_MB>0.03</File_Size_MB>
		</File_Info>
		<Expire_Info>
			<Has_Expire_Info>N</Has_Expire_Info>
			<Expire_Count />
			<Expire_Based_On>Days</Expire_Based_On>
			<Expire_Other_Info />
			<Expire_Month />
			<Expire_Day />
			<Expire_Year />
		</Expire_Info>
	</Program_Info>
	<Program_Descriptions>
		<English>
			<Keywords>Delphi,program,application,source code,free,freeware,RT_HTML,HTML,resource,resource file,compiler,resource compiler,res://,res:// protocol</Keywords>
			<Char_Desc_45>Classes to encapsulate 32 bit resource files</Char_Desc_45>
			<Char_Desc_80>Unit defines classes that encapsulate the Windows 32 bit resource file format.</Char_Desc_80>
			<Char_Desc_250>Unit defines classes that encapsulate the Windows 32 bit resource file format.</Char_Desc_250>
			<Char_Desc_450>PJResFile is a unit that contains classes that encapsulate Windows 32 bit binary resource files and the resources contained in them. The main functionality is provided by two classes. TPJResourceFile encapsulates the contents of a whole resource file and allows it to be edited. TPJResourceEntry encapsulates a single resource and provides access to its raw data via a TStream interface. Helper functions and useful constants are also provided.</Char_Desc_450>
			<Char_Desc_2000>PJResFile is a unit that contains classes that encapsulate Windows 32 bit binary resource files and the resources contained in them. The main functionality is provided by two classes. TPJResourceFile encapsulates the contents of a whole resource file and provides methods and properties for reading, finding, editing, adding and deleting resources. Resource files can be read and written from and tofiles or stream. TPJResourceEntry encapsulates a single resource within the file and provides access to its header properties and to its raw data along with methods to check the identity of the resource. The resource's raw data is made available as a TStream and so is easily read and written using familiar TStream methods. It should noted that the class has no knowledge of resource data formats and sees the data simply as a sequence of bytes. In addition to the two main classes, some helper functions are also provided that assist in working with resource indentifiers. An exception class, EPJResourceFile, is also defined. Exceptions of this class are raised by both the main classes when errors are encountered. Some memory flag constants are defined that are for use with the memory flags field of resource header records. The RT_HTML and RT_MANIFEST resource types they are also defined since they are not defined by Delphi. The unit can either be incorporated in Delphi projects or can be installed into a Delphi package so the unit can be referenced without adding to a project. A detailed description of the classes, along example code for the key methods, is provided in the User Guide.</Char_Desc_2000>
		</English>
	</Program_Descriptions>
	<Web_Info>
		<Application_URLs>
			<Application_Info_URL>http://www.delphidabbler.com/software.php?id=resfile</Application_Info_URL>
			<Application_Order_URL>http://www.delphidabbler.com/software.php?id=resfile</Application_Order_URL>
			<Application_Screenshot_URL>http://www.delphidabbler.com/pad/resfile-scr.gif</Application_Screenshot_URL>
			<Application_Icon_URL>http://www.delphidabbler.com/pad/resfile-ico.gif</Application_Icon_URL>
			<Application_XML_File_URL>http://www.delphidabbler.com/pad/resfile-pad.xml</Application_XML_File_URL>
		</Application_URLs>
		<Download_URLs>
			<Primary_Download_URL>http://www.delphidabbler.com/download.php?file=resfile.zip</Primary_Download_URL>
			<Secondary_Download_URL />
			<Additional_Download_URL_1 />
			<Additional_Download_URL_2 />
		</Download_URLs>
	</Web_Info>
	<Permissions>
		<Distribution_Permissions>The program and source code can be freely distributed providing the copyright and license statements remains attached to the program and source and any modifications are documented.</Distribution_Permissions>
		<EULA>This program is subject to the Mozilla Public License Version 1.1 (the "License"); you may not use this program except in compliance with the License. You may obtain a copy of the License at http://www.mozilla.org/MPL/. Software distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" basis, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the License for the specific language governing rights and limitations under the License.

The Original Code is Resource File Unit.

The Initial Developer of the Original Code is Peter Johnson (http://www.delphidabbler.com/). Portions created by the Initial Developer are Copyright © 2004 Peter Johnson. All Rights Reserved. 

Contributor(s):

The program has copyright and license information contained in the source code and embedded in the executable file and help file. Copyright information is usually displayed in the program's About Box.

All relevant trademarks are acknowledged.</EULA>
	</Permissions>
	<ASP>
		<ASP_FORM>Y</ASP_FORM>
		<ASP_Member>N</ASP_Member>
		<ASP_Member_Number />
	</ASP>
</XML_DIZ_INFO>
